I want to tell you about two experiences that demonstrate how
我想要分享两段经历来展示
software engineering has always been an essential tool in my data science work.
为什么软件工程是我做数据科学工作不可或缺的工具
My first experience is about my previous job,
第一段经历与上一份工作有关
where I've worked as a data scientist at a small startup.
我曾在一家小型创业公司担任数据科学家
There, my work involved several machine learning and deep learning projects,
在那里 我的工作涉及到多个机器学习和深度学习的项目
where personalized shopping experiences for
为用户提供个性化购物体验
users and built analytic tools for the business.
以及为业务构建分析工具
Although I was excited that my work touched on many different areas in data science,
这些工作涉及到数据科学的许多不同领域 我当然会因此而兴奋
one unexpected part was how much software engineering I learned and applied.
但最意想不到的是 我从中学习和应用了很多软件工程的技能
Almost everyone else was more of a software engineer,
几乎所有人都更像是软件工程师
with roles ranging from web and mobile developer to systems architect.
职责范围从 Web 和移动开发到系统架构
To implement my data science ideas and bring them to production,
为了实现我的数据科学思想并将其投入生产
I had to use the proper practices and tools used in software development.
我必须使用软件开发中使用的恰当实践和工具
Applying these practices, really allowed me to collaborate effectively with
应用这些实践 确实让我能够与其他开发人员有效协作
other developers and set up my data science code to work well in production.
也可以使我设置的数据科学代码 在产品中良好运作
Since this specific job was at a startup,
由于这份特定的工作经历是在一个初创公司
I did get more involved in the software engineering side of things,
我确实更多地参与了软件工程方面的工作
than I would at a larger company.
如果在一家大公司则不会如此
But like we mentioned earlier,
但正如我们之前提到的
there are significant benefits to using
作为一名数据科学家
software engineering practices as a data scientist in any context.
在任何情况下使用软件工程实践都会有很大好处
This leads me to my second experience about my first major project.
这就要讲讲我要分享的第二段经历了 关于我的首次大型项目
Before even landing my first data science job,
在我开始第一份数据科学的工作之前
there used to be a calendar app that I organized my life with and loved.
曾经有一个日历应用 我很喜欢并用它来安排自己的生活
When I heard it was being taken down from the App Store,
当听说这个应用在 App 商店下架了之后
I decided to build my own version.
我决定建立自己的版本
I wanted to take it a step further and build
我还想更进一步
the chatbot that would automatically create calendar entries for me,
建立一个聊天机器人 可以自动为我创建日历条目
and answer questions I had about my schedule.
也可以回答我对日程安排的问题
I used my data science skills to create
我使用了数据科学技能创建了
a chatbot that classified messages and generated appropriate responses.
聊天机器人 可以对消息进行分类 并做出恰当的响应
But I didn't know anything about web development,
但是我对 Web 开发一无所知
and wasn't sure where to start.
不知道如何开始开发应用
So, I took an online course in web development.
所以 我参加了一门 Web 开发的在线课程
I figured out how to build a web app that
我了解了如何构建 Web 应用
integrated with the chatbot and Google calendar's API,
将聊天机器人与 Google 日历的 API 进行集成
and set up servers to host it online.
以及如何设置服务器 用来在线托管
In the end, I needed both data science skills and software engineering skills,
最终 我同时需要数据科学技能与软件工程技能
to build my calendar app.
来构建日历应用程序
But it was worth it because I was able to bring
但这是值得的 因为我能够
my vision to reality with this powerful combination of skills.
通过这种强大的技能组合 将幻想变为现实
It can seem intimidating to start learning about
开始学习软件工程 以及
software engineering and how to apply it to your data science work,
其在数据科学工作中的应用 似乎会让人生畏
but that's why we're here,
不过我们讲师就在这里
to walk you through it.
会逐步引导你完成学习
I gained valuable knowledge and skills with resources online and on the job,
通过线上的资源和工作实践 我获取了宝贵的知识和技能
and I know you can too.
你也一定可以
Andrew and I will be showing you some of the tricks we've learned so that
Andrew 和我会分享展示我们学到的技巧
you can start incorporating useful software engineering practices as a data scientist.
帮助作为数据科学家的你 掌握有用的软件工程实践